The Observer Records UA062
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Observer negatives, 1972 -- 1989; 1980 -- 1989; UA062.004; 2.65 Linear Feet; 13 Digital Object(s)
  - Senior Week, 1985; UA062.004.010.00068 (Box 10)
    Senior Week Picnic: Ken (Sucker) McGagh
  - Snow, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00069 (Box 10)
    Sledding: 3/9/83, Al Levenson; Snow Scenes: 11/26/86, Steven Bushell; first Snow, last issue: 12/6/81, Karen Edensword; Traying in Snowstorm: 2/21/83, Al Levenson; Shanty Town of '85-'86: 1986, Chuck Boatwright
    - Shanty town, 1986; UA062.004.010.00069.00001; Boatwright, Chuck (Box 10)
      Anti-apartheid movements; Squatter settlements
    - Shanty town, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00069.00002; Boatwright, Chuck (Box 10)
    - Students construct shanty town, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00069.00003; Boatwright, Chuck (Box 10)
      Anti-apartheid movements; Squatter settlements; People; Students
    - Students construct Shanty town, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00069.00004; Boatwright, Chuck (Box 10)
    - Students construct Shanty town, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00069.00005; Boatwright, Chuck (Box 10)
    - Students construct Shanty town, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00069.00006; Boatwright, Chuck (Box 10)
  - Men's Soccer, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00070 (Box 10)
  - Men's Soccer, 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00071 (Box 10)
    Men's Soccer; Men's Soccer; Unlabeled; Men's Soccer (A-B): 1984; Men's Soccer: 9/28/83, Ken McGagh; Men's Soccer Coach, Lisa Rafin, Women's Soccer: 9/8/83, Ken McGagh
  - Women's Soccer, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00072 (Box 10)
    Soccer(A-B): 9/12, Jon Spielman; Soccer: Carolyn Hine; Women's Varsity (A-C): 10/19, Mark Florence; Soccer (A-B): 9/28, Mark Florence; Women's Soccer(A-C): 10/6/82, Al Levenson; Women's Soccer Game on Thurs: 10/1/81, Peter J.; Soccer; Women's Soccer- Janet the Goalie: 9/23/81, Allen Levenson
  - Women's Soccer, 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00073 (Box 10)
    Women's Soccer: Ken McGagh; Women's Soccer (A-B)
  - Women's Soccer, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00074 (Box 10)
    Women's Soccer (A-B): Ken McGagh
  - Women's Softball, 1984 -- 1985; UA062.004.010.00075 (Box 10)
    Women's Softball: Ken McGagh
  - Women's Softball, 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00076 (Box 10)
    Women's Softball (A-B): Darren Tan
  - Speakers (A), 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00077 (Box 10)
    Guy Anthony: 3/83, Armin Seifart; Sam Adams: 8/10/82, A. Levenson; Maya Angelou (A-B): 2/81, Karen Edensword; Maya Angelou (A-C): 9/26/83.
  - Speakers (B), 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00078 (Box 10)
    Belloti: 10/14/82, Allen Levenson; John Buick: 1/26/83, Izeman; A. Balowon (A-B): 11/11/82, Bernard Pelo; A. Balowan: 11/11/82, Louise Bryan; Norman O Brown (A-C): 9/30/81, Levenson and Edensword; Derek Bok: 3/11/81, Steve Labaton; Senator Julian Bond: 10/8/81, Allen Levenson.
  - Speakers (C), UA062.004.010.00079 (Box 10)
    Calm Down Mama: 4/10/84, Ann Sherpick; Manny Corello: 2/20/84, Ann Sherpick; Clinton: 5/5/82, A. Levenson; Chinese Ambassador: 3/30/1981, S. Morisseau; Cut Lecturer (A-B): 2/24/83, Ken McGagh; Lecturer at Cabot: 10/9, Chuck; Cox: 11/30, Wong.
  - Speakers (D), 1982 -- 1985; UA062.004.010.00080 (Box 10)
    Author (A-B): 11/10/85, Ken McGagh; Dukakis (A-B): 10/14/82, Allen Levenson; Uri? Doigan (A-B): 2/9/84, Ken McGagh; Mary Dain (A-B): 11/7/85, Ken McGagh; Mike Davidson: 12/1/82, Ken McGagh
  - Speakers (F), 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00081 (Box 10)
    Ex-paralyzed football player in Medical School (Jim Ford) (A-B): 9/14/85, Lisa Wong; Family Lecture (A-B): 10/25, Lisa Wong; Betty Friedar (A-B): 3/8/84, Ken McGagh; Lecture, Food Aid (A-B): 3/9/83, Ken McGagh; French Ambassador: 11/17/83, Ken McGagh
  - Speakers (G), 1984 -- 1985; UA062.004.010.00082 (Box 10)
    Cheryl Hart (A-B): 2/1/84, Dick Gregory; Grenada (A-B): 11/17/85, Ken McGagh; Lesley Gelb Lecture (A-B): 2/20/85, Dan Thornton
  - Speakers (H), 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00083 (Box 10)
    A Invite of Iran?: 4/27/82, A. Levenson; Dr. Hubbard: 3/17/84, Ann Sherpick; Michael Harrington (A-C): 10/16/81, Karen Edensword; Verner Hoffman (A-C): 11/15/82, Ken McGagh
  - Speakers, Students, Staff (J), 1980 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00084 (Box 10)
    Judiciary and T.J. Johnson: 9/15/81, Mark Golden; T.J.-Tom Johnson, Afro-American: 2/24/82, Allen Levenson; Paula Jones: 12/9/82, Izeman; Ellen Jacobs and Ian (?) Watson (A-B): 4/8/82, Al Levenson
  - Speakers (K), 1980 -- 1981; UA062.004.010.00085 (Box 10)
    Robert Klien (A-B): 10/30/81, Allen Levenson; Tibetan Monk, Religious Department, Rinpoche Kalsang (A-B): 1980, Karen Edensword; Joe Kennedy Jr.: 10/13/82, Al Levenson; M. Kessel: 4/4/84, Ann Sherpick; Glenn Kurtz?, Classical Guitar (A-B): 10/19/81, Karen Edensword
  - Speakers (L), 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00086 (Box 10)
    Richard Loenwarter CBS 60 Minutes (A-C): 3/2/83; Lebanon Lecture (A-C): 3/14/84, Ken McGagh; Unlabeled; Unlabeled; Bruce Laingen (A-C):11/17/82, Ken McGagh; Lecture: 11/16, Mark Florence; Bob Lobel: 2/23/83, Al Levenson
  - Speakers (M), 1982 -- 1983; UA062.004.010.00087 (Box 10)
    Musil and Colonel Taylor: 11/10/82, Allen Levenson; Evelyn Murphy (A-B): Allen Levenson; Robert Moore, Vietnam Vet (A-B): 2/23/83, Ann Sherpick
  - Speakers (N), 1983 -- 1985; UA062.004.010.00088 (Box 10)
    Nicaragua: 5/5/83, Al Levenson; Ralph Wadar(A-B): 4/21/85, Ken McGagh; Nazi War Criminals(A-B): 4/12/84, Ken McGagh; Nazi Holacaust(A-B): 4/14/83, Ken McGagh; Nurse(?)(Lebenon)(A-B): 2/29/84, Ann Sherpick; Nuclear Referendum: 11/83, R. Lipset
  - Special Interest Housing, 1980 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00089 (Box 10)
    Crafts House & Pottery (A-B): 4/22/1981, Karen Edensword; Crafts House (A-B): 12/8/83, Ken McGagh; Joseph Kamibar, Crafts House, TU Librarian: 12/3/1980, Cheryl Hart; Environmentalist House (A-C): 9/21/83, Lisa Wong; Hall House (A-C): 10/25/83, Paul Fold I; Culture House (A-B): 3/3/81, Amy Liss; Capen House: 12/1/81, Allen Levenson; Culture Houses: 2/17/84, Ken McGagh; International House: no date
  - Sprague, 1983; UA062.004.010.00090 (Box 10)
    Sprague: 3/16/83, Al Levenson; Sprague: 3/17/83, Al Levenson; Sprague: 3/17/83, Al Levenson; Sprague (A-B): 3/1/83, Al Levenson
  - Spring, 1987; UA062.004.010.00091 (Box 10)
    Steven Bushell
  - Squash, 1981 -- 1982; UA062.004.010.00092 (Box 10)
    Mark Boshar and Squash (A-B): 2/3; Squash, Guys and Girls Captains: 10/9/81, Allen Levenson; Men's Squash (A- B): 12/1/81, Allen Levenson; Squash Practice, Player Mike Scott, Only Freshman: 2/2/82, JB Lyon
  - Squash, 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00093 (Box 10)
    Girl's Squash: 3/9/83, Al Levenson; Men's Squash (A-C): 3/21/83, Al Levenson
  - Squash, 1982 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00094; Bushnell, Steven (Box 10)
    Squash (A-B): December 7, Wong; M Squash: 2/16/86, Darren Tan; Men's Squash (A-B): 2/3/86, Chuck Boatwright; Men's Squash: 12/1/82, Al Levenson On January 3, 2013, DCA staff added additional negatives taken by Steven Bushnell (accession 2013.061).
  - The Stompers, UA062.004.010.00095 (Box 10)
    The Stompers at Cohen (A-D): Karen Edensword
  - Students (Unidentified), 1984; UA062.004.010.00096 (Box 10)
    People (Unknown) No. 4; People No. 1: '84
  - Students (Unidentified), 1982 -- 1985; UA062.004.010.00097 (Box 10)
    People (A-B): 10/23/85, Chuck Boatright; People on Campus: 4/13/82, A Levenson; Person Painting: 5/8/82, Allen Levenson
  - Students (Unidentified), 1984; UA062.004.010.00098 (Box 10)
  - Students (A), 1985 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00099 (Box 10)
    Theresa Allen: 2/12/86, Stephanie Wolk; Doug Adams: 2/10/87, Chuck Boatwright; Kathy Ambroso: 3/6/85, Dan Thornton
  - Students (B), 1987; UA062.004.010.00100 (Box 10)
    Dierdre Burns: Chuck Boatwright
  - Students (D), 1984 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00101 (Box 10)
    Unlabeled: 12/26/86, Ejyo Kataguri; Tony Dennis Young Republicans (A-B): 10/3/84, R. Rodgers
  - Students (G), 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00102 (Box 10)
    Jeff Ganz; John Ginsberg: 10/28/87, Steve Bushell; Jeff Ganz: 9/3/86; Jeff Ganz: 1/27/87, Chuck Boatwright; Jeff Ganz: 1985/86; Jeff Ganz: 4/14/87, Steven Bushell
  - Students (H), 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00103 (Box 10)
    Tracy Hahn: 1/21/87, Sheryl Kalis; Mark Hurly: 4/9/86, Ejyo Kataguri; Tracy Hahn: 4/9/86, Sheryl Kalis; Tracy Hahn (A-B): 10/16/86; Mary Hansen: 3/26/86, Ellen Sackelman; Rusty Hashin: 10/29/87, Steve Bushell
  - Students (K), 1987; UA062.004.010.00104 (Box 10)
    Ian Kremmer: Chuck Boatwright
  - Students (M), 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00105 (Box 10)
    Meghan McCaffrey: 10/86; Stephanie Wolk; Meagan McCaffrey: 1/21/87, Sheryl Kalis; Jean Marshal: 10/29/86, Chuck Boatwright
  - Students (O, N and P), 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.010.00106 (Box 10)
    Robert Patz: 2/12/86, Stephanie Wolk; Jose Nietro: 2/10/87, Chuck Boatwright; Mike Ubadia (A-B): 2/18/86, Chuck Boatwright
  - Students (R), 1984 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00107 (Box 10)
    Unlabeled (A-B): 1/29/86, Chuck Boatwright; Some Broad: Steven; Beth Rosen: 11/84, Dan Thornton; Runner: 12/5/85, Ken McGagh
  - Students (S), 1987; UA062.004.010.00108 (Box 10)
    Bill Shien at the Pub (A-B): Chuck Boatwright; Armin Seifart
  - Students (T), 1982 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00109 (Box 10)
    Unlabeled: 11/25/86, Chuck Boatwright; B Tudden: 3/22/82, A Levenson; Kevin Thurm (A-B): 12/1/82, Allen Levenson; Jim Towny: 3/22/82, A. Levenson; Wendy Thurm: 4/9/86, Sheryl Kalis; Cliff Tasner: 1/30/85, Dan Thornton; Kevin Thurm (A-B): 9/8/81, Bruce Torrence; Mike Tabscott: 9/83, Jon Spielman; Kevin Thurm: 1/27/82, Peter Jacobi; Kevin Thurm: A. Balowon, Kevin Thurm: 2/10/82, Allen Levenson
  - Swimming, 1980; UA062.004.010.00110 (Box 10)
    Men's Swim 'Coach'
  - Men's Swimming, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.004.010.00111 (Box 10)
    Swimming and Diving '80: 1980, Nora McTiernan; Men's Swimming (A-D): 1979
  - Men's Swimming, 1982; UA062.004.010.00112 (Box 10)
    Men's Swim: 11/17/82, Izeman; Men's Swim: 11/17/82, Izeman; Men's Swim '82: 11/17/82, Izeman; Swimming Pool: 1/26/82, Al Levenson; Men's Swimming (A-B): 11/17/82, Al Levenson
  - Men's Swimming, 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00113 (Box 10)
    Men's Swimming (A-B): 2/19/84, Ken; Men's Swimming (A-B): 1/26/84, Ken McGagh; Swimming-Wong: 2/2/83, Al Levenson
  - Men's Swimming, 1985 -- 1988; UA062.004.010.00114 (Box 10)
    M-Swim: 2/19/86, Ejyo Kataguri; M-Swim ('85-'86) (A-C): 1986, Chuck Boatwright; Men's Swim: Ellen Sackelman; Men's Swim: Ellen Sackelman; Men's Swimming and Jonathan Wilson (A-B): Ellen Sackelman; Men's Swimming (A-C): 2/2/86, Chuck Boatwright; Men's Swim Team and Women's Track: 1/28, Stephanie Wolk; Men's Swimming: 1/28, Stephanie Wolk; Men's Swimming Nationals: Armin Seifart
  - Women's Swimming, 1979 -- 1980; UA062.004.010.00115 (Box 10)
    Women's Swim (A-B): Mary Kay
  - Women's Swimming, 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.010.00116 (Box 10)
    Women's Swimming (A-C): 1/18/83, Ken McGagh; Brenda Kay Swimming (A-B): 2/3/84, Ken McGagh; Men's Swimming (A-B): 2/8/84, Dan Thornton; Women's Swim (A-C): 2/9/84, Ken McGagh; Women's Swimming (A-C): 2/28/84, Dan Thornton; Women' s Swimming: 1/25/83, Armin Seifart; Women's Diving, Women's Swimming: 3/9/83, Ken McGagh; Women's Swim: 2/15/84, Ken McGagh
  - Women's Swimming, 1984 -- 1986; UA062.004.010.00117 (Box 10)
    Women's Swim Team: 2/5/84, Julia Gordon; Women's Swimming: 2/19/86, Ejyo Kataguri
  - (T), 1981 -- 1988; UA062.004.011.00001 (Box 11)
    Tufts Touchstore Founders: 3/17/82, Al Levenson; Television: Ken McGagh; Transfer Applications (A-B): 2/17/81, Allen Levenson; T.V. Tryouts Lines (A-B): 3/9/83, Allen Levenson; Transfer Students (Jackie London, Nick Orlou): 2/2/84, Ann Sherpick; Tai Chi (A-B): 2/28/84, Dan Thornton; TSR Managers (A-C): 2/17/82, Al Levenson; Take-Five Band (A-B): 9/28/83, Ken McGagh; Tutoring: 9/8/82, Al Levenson; TA's: 3/17/83, Al Levenson; TSR at Eaton: 2/16/88, Al Levenson; Davis T-stop: 10/17/86, Steven Bushell, TSL: 10/12/83, Betsy Rigby (only contact sheets, no negatives)
  - Tennis, 1979; UA062.004.011.00002 (Box 11)
    Football (!) Tennis
  - Tennis (Men), 1982 -- 1983; UA062.004.011.00003 (Box 11)
    Men's Tennis, Not Usable (A-B): 3/17/82, A. Levenson; Bill Friend (A-B): 5/5/82, Allen Levenson; Eric Shat (A-B): 5/26/82, Al Levenson; Men's Tennis: 5/5/83, Al Levenson; Men's Tennis (A-C): 4/21/82, Al Levenson; Tennis: Peter Ho, Tennis (A-C): 4/18/83, Al Levenson
  - Tennis (Men), 1984; UA062.004.011.00004 (Box 11)
    Men's Tennis: Ken McGagh
  - Men's Tennis, 1986 -- 1987; UA062.004.011.00005 (Box 11)
    Tennis, Chris Davita; Men's Tennis (A-C): Sheryl Kalis; Unlabeled contact sheet of tennis
  - Tennis (Women), 1980 -- 1982; UA062.004.011.00006 (Box 11)
    Tennis (Woman's): 9/81, Jennifer Krogh; Carolyn Hine Tennis 80 (A-B): Jim Watson?: 5/26/82, A Levenson; Girls Tennis (A-C): 10/6/82, Al Levenson; Women's Tennis: 9/30/81, Allen Levenson
  - Tennis (Women), 1983 -- 1984; UA062.004.011.00007 (Box 11)
    Women's Tennis (A-C): 1984; Sports-Tennis-Women (A-C): 9/21/83, Mark Florence; Tennis: 9/28, Mark Florence
  - Women's Tennis, 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.011.00008 (Box 11)
    Ladies Tennis(A-C): Chuck Boatright; Pictures of Women's Tennis: Steven Bushell
  - TMC, 1981 -- 1984; UA062.004.011.00009 (Box 11)
    Rock Climbing (A-C): 2/23/84, Ken McGagh; TMC (A-C): 10/21/81, Allen Levenson
  - Torn Ticket, 1984; UA062.004.011.00010 (Box 11)
    Fiddler on the Roof:Ken McGagh; Fiddler on the Roof (A-C): Ken McGagh
  - TPAC, 1981 -- 1986; UA062.004.011.00011 (Box 11)
    TPAC/SPS Debate (A-B): 11/17/82, Ken McGagh; TPAC Meeting (A-C): 11/2/81, Allen Levenson; TPAC: 10/31/86, Steve Bushell; Girl Running: 3/9/83, Allen Levenson
  - Men's Track, 1980 -- 1981; UA062.004.011.00012 (Box 11)
    Shotput and Track: 1/25/80; Track: 12/8/81, Allen Levenson; Men's Track, Powderhouse, No Parking: 11/10/81, Peter Jacobs
  - Men's Track 1982-1983, UA062.004.011.00013 (Box 11)
    Track (A-C): Ken McGagh; Men's Track: 2/23/83, Allen Levenson; Men's Track (A-C): 4/28/83, Ken McGagh; Track (A-B): 1/7/82, Allen Levenson; Track-Shotput Team: 2/2/83, Allen Levenson; Track-Shotput (A-B): 3/22/82, Allen Levenson
  - Men's Track, 1984 -- 1986; UA062.004.011.00014 (Box 11)
    Track(A-B): 1986, Chuck Boatright; Men's Indoor Track: 2/11/84, Dan Thornton; No Label (Men's Track)(A-C)
  - Women's Track, 1982 -- 1984; UA062.004.011.00015 (Box 11)
    Women's Track (A-C): 1/28/84, Ken McGagh; Women's Track: Linda Dureya; Women's Track: 4/13/82, Allen Levenson; No Label (Women's Track)
  - Track (Women), 1985 -- 1986; UA062.004.011.00016 (Box 11)
    Women's Track(A-B): 2/3/86, Chuck Boatright; TUTV Editing Room: 2/5/86, Julia Gordon; Track (A-B): 2/19/86, Julia Gordon; Women's Track: 1/28, Stephanie Wolk; Women's Track: 9/26/86, Ken McGagh; Women's Track: 3/12/86, Darren Tan; Women's Track: 1/26/85, Ken McGagh
  - TSR, UA062.004.011.00017 (Box 11)
    Tom Alpern TSR in Curtis: K. E.
  - Tufts PIRG, UA062.004.011.00018 (Box 11)
    Alison A (?) T-PIRG: A. Levenson
  - Tufts PIRG, 1983; UA062.004.011.00019 (Box 11)
    Tufts PIRG Meeting: Mary-Tara Ward
  - TUTV, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.011.00020 (Box 11)
    TUTV (A-C): 12/2/81; TUTV (A-C): 10/13/83, Ken McGagh
  - Wessell Library, 1981 -- 1983; UA062.004.011.00021 (Box 11)
    Library-Finals: 10/8/82, A. Levenson; Library: 12/1/83, Ken McGagh; Library: 2/2/83, Al Levenson; Library: 3/3/82, Allen Levenson; Library Study Tom Bendheim: 2/2/82, J.B. Lyon; Library (A-B): 11/11/81, Karen Edensword; Library Reference Room Jeff: 9/21/83, Ken McGagh; Library: 2/2/83, Allen Levenson
  - Wessell Library, 1984; UA062.004.011.00022 (Box 11)
    Reserve Room:Dan Thornton